<idea-plugin>
    <id>se.seedba.jetbrains</id>
    <name>SeedBase</name>
    <vendor url="https://seedba.se">SeedBase</vendor>

    <description><![CDATA[
        Browse your <a href="https://seedba.se">SeedBase</a> projects, generate realistic synthetic
        test data and pull SQL/CSV/JSON seeds straight into your project &mdash; without leaving the IDE.
        <ul>
            <li><b>SeedBase tool window</b>: all projects with their generations at a glance</li>
            <li><b>Generate Data</b>: kick off a generation and get notified when it completes</li>
            <li><b>Pull into Project</b>: download a generation as SQL, CSV or JSON and open it in the editor</li>
            <li><b>Secure login</b>: browser-based authorization, token stored in the IDE's Password Safe</li>
        </ul>
        <p><b>Getting started:</b> create a <b>free</b> account at
        <a href="https://seedba.se/register">seedba.se</a> (no credit card), then click the key icon in
        the tool window to sign in. The free tier is enough to generate full, foreign-key-consistent
        datasets for your schema.</p>
        <p>More about the plugin: <a href="https://seedba.se/jetbrains">seedba.se/jetbrains</a>.</p>
    ]]></description>

    <change-notes><![CDATA[
        <b>0.2.3</b>
        <ul>
            <li>Clearer upgrade hint: when an export format is not available on your plan (for example Parquet on the Free plan), the error now points to upgrading to Pro instead of showing a generic failure. Free includes SQL, CSV and JSON.</li>
            <li>Sign-in no longer briefly blocks the UI thread: the whole login (initiate + poll) now runs in the background.</li>
        </ul>
        <b>0.2.2</b>
        <ul>
            <li>Fixed a UI freeze: the credential store is no longer read on the EDT (tool window open and toolbar updates were doing a synchronous keychain lookup). Login state is now cached in memory and the token is read off the UI thread.</li>
        </ul>
        <b>0.2.1</b>
        <ul>
            <li>Clearer onboarding: the tool window and description now point to the free seedba.se account needed to sign in</li>
            <li>Replaced deprecated platform APIs (credential store, list renderer) for forward compatibility with 2026.2+</li>
        </ul>
        <b>0.2.0</b>
        <ul>
            <li><b>Push Schema</b>: turn workspace schema files into a SeedBase project schema &mdash; Django
                <code>models.py</code> (all apps combined automatically), Prisma and SQL, with a
                detect preview and confirmation before applying</li>
        </ul>
        <b>0.1.0</b>
        <ul>
            <li>Initial release: tool window with projects &amp; generations, browser-based login
                (Password Safe), Generate Data, Pull SQL/CSV/JSON, Open in Browser</li>
        </ul>
    ]]></change-notes>

    <depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends>

    <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
        <toolWindow id="SeedBase" anchor="right" icon="/icons/seedbase.svg"
                    factoryClass="se.seedba.jetbrains.toolwindow.SeedbaseToolWindowFactory"/>
        <notificationGroup id="SeedBase" displayType="BALLOON"/>
    </extensions>
</idea-plugin>
